The
Wizard
Tire tight, lads. This witch is a wily one.
Suffer not a witch to live, says I.
Tell me where my treasure is, witch. Your wicked games end here and now.
You won't get a word from me.
Serena, please. If you ever truly loved me, you wouldn't be doing this.
I'm not even doing anything, Roderick. Your treasure is cursed.
Now, Captain, she'll never tell. Make her pay for her defiance!
Last chance, witch.
I did love you.
Oh.
Ignore her, lads. It's trickery.
look
roger cross from this day forward you are cursed
you will never find your treasure and you will never truly die
you will wander this island as a ghost knowing no joy
no love only pain like the pain you caused me i will not
die on land you simply will not die at all
thus ends the tale of captain
roderick cross a bloodthirsty cutthroat destined to haunt this island for all
eternity that was all the invitation
of course not angelo there's a qr code
this is what the invitation says britain with usual pinster melodrama
christian w pinster the third invites you to a special weekend getaway
full of adventure mystery and the chance to find the long lost cross
treasure avast ye may east prepare for the adventure of a lifetime
okay come on everybody we all know that preston is tier one at planning parties
ruby it sounds like more than just a party all this talk of
pirates and buried treasure has me all excited i wouldn't exactly call this tier one now last year's
trip to dubai however
good yay ethan just a little seasick from the trip i know things have been a little rocky with
us but maybe this weekend is a good chance for us to rekindle the flame maybe i just need to
get rid of these damn sea legs got the remedy for those sea legs doctor recommended come on kip really
you couldn't leave a home for one weekend i don't know dad can you not be a buzzkill for one weekend
okay everybody why don't we take a selfie to celebrate the beginning of our fun friendly
harmonious weekend okay everybody back here thank you angelo all right and smile
perfect thank you guys this will be fun
guys
guys you shouldn't be here this island is cursed
when the plan is full roger cross will walk again he starts his first
find it no one no one will survive easy old timer you've been warned leave and live
or stay and die that choice is yours
what the hell was that do you guys think that we should maybe like uh listen to that guy guys
it's all part of the act someone pressed and hired to scare us i mean do you really
think some pirate ghost is out here murdering people for gold it'd be all over the news
or
it could be a massive montage cover-up one of those government conspiracy to hide the truth
and what truth would that be kip the dip like a giant lake monster swimming around out there
looking to feast on our flesh and wear our bodies like halloween costumes and and take our candy you
know that kip shall we go looks like preston didn't arrange for a ride so we got a little
bit of a hike if that's the case then you're carrying my bags
oh
what the hell you scared the fuck out of me i certainly hope not
oh thanks baby i was just trying to have some fun fun yesterday
you just have to scare me you know it's not supposed to be that kind of weekend
it's not a weekend full of cheap scares what kind of weekend would it be baby
i just i was hoping it was about discovering hidden treasure i see some booty
shut up shall i shiver your timbers make it quickly
who knows she knows
it's all right it's not what it looks like we're uh looking for contacts
It appears you have caught us in an awkward position.
It looks fine from this vantage point.
I simply came to inform you that your guests have arrived.
Oh, yes, yes, um, I'm going to handle affairs here, uh, before I meet the landlubbers.
Why don't you go on ahead?
I'll meet up with you shortly.
Good idea.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Wow.
This place is amazing.
How much do you think this set him back?
Knowing Preston, a big chunk of his inheritance.
Ahoy there, my deities!
Hey!
All right.
Oh, my God!
Y'all are here!
Oh, I didn't think y'all would be here.
Oh, y'all made it.
What the fuck, man?
Oh, what's going on?
Oh.
Thanks, man.
All right.
How are y'all doing?
Hope your voyage by sea wasn't too choppy.
Yeah, other than Willow, it was great.
Me and Boots, you know.
Well, you know how it is.
If the island was big enough for a landing strip, I could have definitely got you guys
to pay my check.
But, uh, speaking of landing strips.
Heh.
I'd like to introduce you guys to the beautiful and lovely Miss Harley Da Silva, soon to be Sean, babe.
BAM!
Mrs. Harley Pinster.
Yeah, we're getting married!
We're getting shot! That's what I'm trying to say! That's what I'm trying to say!
Oh my god! You're gonna have to tell us all about how you and our little Preston met.
Congrats, man. I'm happy for ya.
I appreciate you.
Hey, you alright? You good?
Oh, yeah. The seasickness has really hit her.
What's this about sea legs?
Kip!
Weren't you just behind us?
No. I was in front of you.
Alright, let's put on our bathing suits, and let's soak up the sun before sundown, and obviously that's when the games gonna begin. Come on.
Games?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Games. Come on, guys. Come on. Come on.
I'm so excited to show it to you.
Oh my gosh.
Yeah, it's written on the wall.
So, what do you guys think?
Oh, man. This is awesome.
Ooh! Are these real?
Hey, rooms!
Yeah?
Catch!
Okay.
Still any good?
Let's see.
Ha!
Okay.
Hi-yah!
Woo!
Better than you in my sleep.
Haha.
So, what do you say?
Um, uncle.
Uh-huh.
Auntie?
Mama.
Weird.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you guys very much.
Sorry.
That was tonight's entertainment, everyone. Give them a round of applause. Thank you.
YouTube Club.
Birds.
Come here.
I got something special for y'all.
Here it is.
The master bedroom for the power couple.
Please, feel free to look around.
Pretty nice if you ignore the very white paint, the popcorn ceilings, and that mermaid on the wall.
Yeah.
At least the view is amazing.
Is that a good day?
Why, yes it is.
To clean your little bum-bum bag.
Now,
I did use it once.
What a woman won't do.
Oh, yeah.
And, uh,
you guys having the best room and all,
I trust
that you'll make this room
go a-rockin'.
That means sex.
You bet.
Come here, I'll sass a crack at you tonight.
Get up, get up, get up.
You know,
I could go for a good boat rockin'.
Wanna board S.S.E.?
Serious right now?
It was a bad joke.
But it's been months.
Can't we get past what happened?
Can we just get back to being us?
It's not just something you can get over.
I'll never understand how you could just move on like nothing happened.
I didn't even do anything.
Guess we're gonna need a bigger boat.
I'll give you a fair warning before we bully way.
Blow the man down.
Blow the man down, bullies.
Blow him right back to Liverpool town.
Give me some time to do this.
Blow the man down.
Oh, don't be scared.
Who are you?
Are you with the group that came here?
You should have heeded my warning and left the island while there's still time.
When the full moon rises, it'll bring all the wicked things.
Oh, I'm well aware.
For you see,
I am one of them.
One of the wicked things.
You crazy bitch.
Hey, can't you know?
Let this offering to the great gods of the deep
allow that which was dead to roam
and reclaim what's left to us.
Come in, Nicole.
Just now.
Now, Rebulon.
Soon the blood moon will rise in the dark sky.
And he shall rise from the sea.
From the sea.
Come on.
With lots of pineapples, you know that kind of vibe.
That sounds beautiful.
But I have a question.
Have you thought anything about your dress yet?
Yes, I found the perfect dress.
Thanks for joining the party.
Hey, guys.
What's wrong, Willow?
Nothing.
So seasick, I guess.
Yeah, okay, Willow, you can stop fucking around.
We've all known you long enough to know that something is not right.
Yeah, come on, tell us.
Okay, fine.
But it's not like that.
What is it like?
Whoa.
Easy, big fella.
I'm sorry.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
All right, all right, all right.
You know what? I've seen enough.
All right.
Hey.
Relax.
Guys.
Let me go.
All right.
Hold on.
Really?
Not until you tell us what's got your panties in a bunch.
I'll never talk.
Ethan and I are going through a bit of a rough patch.
It's been getting worse the past couple months.
Well, I mean, that could only mean one thing, right?
That he cheated on you?
I knew he was a cheater.
No, no, you didn't cheat.
I did.
Oh, Willow, I did not ever expect to hear those words leave your mouth.
I didn't mean it.
I was in a weird headspace.
I was stressed at work.
They were expecting so much out of me.
Crazy hours, busier workload.
I've met someone who offered to help me.
Why wasn't I enough?
I mean, I did everything right, and she's still straight.
Listen, it's not your fault.
You did nothing wrong.
I can't fucking believe it.
Who was it?
Some giant douchebag from our work.
Ugh, it's always those giant douchebags from work.
They don't operate like we do.
Like real men.
So what did you do when she finally told you?
I forgave her right away.
Oh my god.
He forgave you right away?
That's gross and reeks of desperation.
Well, I don't know.
Maybe he just loves her.
I don't know.
I honestly was with someone that was okay with me stepping out, and he gave me the ick.
Well, did he give you the ick?
Yeah.
That's the thing, though.
Mr. Liberty forgave me right away, but at the same time, I wanted him to fight for me.
Yeah, that sounds weird.
No, it doesn't.
Because you are a queen, and he should fight for you.
I don't know if you guys, like, understand what's going on here, though.
The more time passes, the more distant I feel myself growing from him.
So, what are you going to do?
I love him.
I'm not in love.
I guess I'm just ready to move on.
So what's the plan?
Plan?
Simple.
I'm going to remind Willow of the guy she fell in love with.
Yeah.
I'm not going to let this little speed bump stop us.
I'm going to win her back, or I'm going to die trying.
Hell yeah!
Heck yeah!
Yeah.
I just felt a breakthrough, y'all.
I just felt a breakthrough.
And you know what it calls for?
One big heterosexual male group hug!
Bring it in, guys.
Bring it in.
What the fuck?
I don't know.
What is this?
Some sort of homoerotic show of affection and bonding?
Yeah.
Come here, you pothead.
Am I not getting my notifications?
What the fuck, you guys?
Get in here.
What are we crying about?
Here you go.
Thank you.
My name is
It's such a shame really.
Yeah.
I always thought what they had was perfect.
Yeah, I kind of thought they'd be together forever.
I hope they work it out though.
No, no.
I used to think that was what I wanted in a relationship, but now I am not so sure.
What the fuck?
to my dearest and closest friends you have no idea what this means to me
you guys making the trip all the way here just to be here
together man from the bottom of my heart
you guys got to meet my amazing harley
yeah she gets to meet my not so amazing friends
i'm just serious
that's not even the best part you guys because after this trip
two of you will be walking away with a butt load of money finally getting to the good stuff
so how does one walk away with a butt load of money
girl i thought
you were
i thought you were
i thought you never asked
babes hit my music
i formally introduce to you the lovely and mysterious
saraya
sarai
way
three
code took us to. He was some pirate captain that had his treasure stolen from him, and
some witch put a curse on him. It happened on this very island. In fact,
you all now sit precisely where Cross met his demise. But his soul remains trapped here,
doomed to forever roam until he is reunited with his stolen gold. This gold.
Come on, just sit there. Come on. Quick, quick, quick.
Oh my god. Is this real?
One hundred percent. From the treasure of Captain Roderick Cross.
No way.
Yes way.
How is that possible?
Soraya played a very crucial part in helping me find this treasure.
And so, the game begins. Under some of your chairs lies three maps.
Now, there's only three maps, so I've divided you guys into three groups. Two couples.
Two couples.
And a group of weirdos.
Oh.
Oh, that's us.
Weird and weirdos.
Yeah?
You must work together in order to solve the riddles to find the hidden treasure.
Once you find it, it is yours for the taking.
But that's for...
Don't eat it all! No! Stop! No, cracker! Stop it! No!
Sorry about that.
Where are the weirdos?
That's for tomorrow morning.
So rest up.
But until then, the night's still young, my friends.
So let's party!
Yeah!
You know, winning that money would be an amazing start for a better life.
Yeah. Yeah, it would. But I just hope the money doesn't, like, cause any issues between us, you know?
What do you mean?
She means that money is the root of all evil, man.
People do anything for some scratch.
Preston probably thinks he's doing right.
He probably thinks he's doing right by us, but I think she's right.
It won't change us for the worse.
We're a team.
One for all.
And all for one!
All right, you lunatics, we're officially in this together, so I'm gonna go get some rest, and you guys should too.
Night, Rubes.
Good night, Ruby.
Good night.
You know, if money doesn't get in the way, time will.
What do you mean?
You don't want to go your entire life living with regret.
Just thinking what would've happened if you'd actually gone after true happiness.
You know, Kip, you don't say a whole hell of a lot.
But when you do...
You're so wise and full of insight.
It's not me.
It's those hot fudge sundaes with the double scoops and the hot fudge and the nuts and the...
I don't know, I don't know.
It's the weed.
Well, I'm gonna head inside.
You don't fall asleep out here, okay?
I am one with the earth.
It is all my bed.
Okay.
This money could be a life changer.
It could buy our dream wedding, honeymoon, and a house.
I know, babe.
We're gonna have to bring our A-game if we're gonna win this.
It's not a matter of if.
It's a matter of when we're gonna win.
Now...
Speaking of A-game, are you all stretched out?
Oh, you know it.
Are you ready for me?
Ready, willing, and able.
Get on your hands and knees, maggot.
And turn around.
Harder!
Who's my naughty little bitch?
Woo!
Yeah!
It's Rach.
Hey, A-game,
you ready for the trip or what?
Ready to go.
Ready for the camera?
Ready for the camera.
Ready to go.
Now you can enjoy the show.
We'll see you next time.
Yes!
Go.
Reclaim your gold.
And behold what's more.
You remind me of someone I found very unpleasant.
Now tell me which, what games are you playing?
I...
Speak or die in the deep.
I only wish to aid you in your revenge.
Why on this blue world would you want to do that, little raven?
I don't care.
I give you a warning.
Only one.
Cross me and die.
But you will die.
I...
...
Winning could put us in a good place to start over.
We could get back to finding who we are.
No, I never forgot who we were.
Being happy doesn't need to take a lot of money.
Just being us is a good start.
I'm not quite ready for bed yet.
I have to take a shower.
You rest.
You have a busy day tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Please, just get back to me, Willow.
Miss you.
Ethan?
Fuck.
What?
No time.
I've been doing this for a week and a half now,
plus, we're running late,
so I'm wound up bunch of Hygraneous
Okay?
I know, I know.
We will, how long?
Like, you know, we should buy furniture,
baby.
Yeah, I think we should.
Oh, we're running late.
I'm so busy.
I wonder how you are.
I'll see you next time.
Last night was amazing.
I don't know what got into you.
Oh, like you said.
You got my sights set on a bigger prize.
Ooh, I guess they're good now.
Yeah, I guess there's hope for mankind after all.
Just like we practiced.
We're in this to win this.
Yeah, babe.
We're unstoppable.
They have no drive.
They have no determination.
They're weak.
We're the 80.
The alphas.
I'm the alpha beta boy.
Avast ye mateys.
Batten down the hutters.
For we have treasure to hunt.
Hold up your doubloons.
Each of you has one.
This is part of the treasure.
The first person to discover the treasure
must add the doubloon to it.
The first people to do so will reap great treasure
that would make Blackbeard himself
tighten in his pants.
Yeah?
Yeah, but are the costumes totally...
necessary or...
They're so fun.
And you look hot.
Oh, yeah.
When don't I?
Does that mean we can start?
Um...
Oh, yeah.
Let the games...
BEGIN!
They seem serious.
Yeah.
But they're going the wrong way.
Oh.
Ah.
I'm coming aboard.
And where is mine?
Well?
In there.
Of course it is.
Finally.
Seven pieces shy.
Where is the rest
of my Gold Witch?
Speak now.
Or never again.
There are others
on this island.
Seven others.
And they each have one piece.
They're playing a game.
They must find your treasure
and put the seven pieces back.
Sit tight, Witch.
I have some scallywags to find.
The seven must
be returned.
Let's go.
Time to play!
Easy there. It's just us.
It's time to play.
Why are you dressed like that?
Pirate games.
Remember?
The whole reason we're on this island?
Yeah.
I remember.
I told you not to pass out here, man.
I was going to go in,
but that weird
witchy lady came by
and shotgun weed into my face.
I just passed out here.
That's a weird dream,
Sal.
Yeah, with her involved in it,
they're probably pretty amazing.
No.
She just showed up
and started dancing by the water
and then that dead pirate guy
came out of the water
and killed her.
That's all I remember.
Jesus, man.
Lay off the green
for a while.
Or just do that.
Well, you ready to go now?
You good?
Everyone else already started.
Yeah.
Lead the way, dollface.
Babe.
I think we're going the wrong way.
This map
is just one big puzzle.
After you crashed last night,
I stayed up all night
studying it.
And from what I remember
of the island as we sailed in,
I've determined that this
is where we need to go.
I fucking love this girl!
I'm the brains,
and you, my darling,
are the muscle.
That makes me the boss.
So if you're done questioning me,
then we've got treasure to find.
Sorry, mistress.
Much better.
Oh.
This has to be that strange
rock structure from the map.
We are
gonna win, no doubt.
Yeah, well, if we continue
this way,
we should lead us right to the bluffs.
Why are we just standing here?
This is it.
It has to be in this cave.
There's no one else in sight.
We're really gonna do this.
Fifteen men on a dead man's chest.
Yo ho ho
and a bottle of rum.
Who's that?
Another actor, probably.
Preston's really going all out.
Yo ho ho
and a bottle of rum.
You look amazing.
Your costume's way better than ours.
I smell some of my
missing gold.
Let me guess.
You beguired in the treasure.
So what do we do?
Give this to you and you take us to it?
It's all ours, babe!
No!
Yes, witch.
Run.
Fifteen men, stiff and stark.
Yo ho ho
and a bottle of rum.
Ten of the men had the
murder mark.
It was a cut list, like,
for an ounce of lead
or a gaping hole in a
battered head.
Yo ho ho
and a bottle of rum.
There they lie,
dare my eyes,
staring up that
paradise.
All souls bound,
just contra wise.
Yo ho ho
and a bottle of rum.
Why are you doing this?
Gold?
That's what you want?
We were going to
give it to you anyway.
That's a good lass.
So I give you a choice.
Fast and painless
or slow and excruciating.
Please.
I gave you the gold.
Just let me live.
I'm sorry, lass.
Cold as the sea.
Ah.
Okay.
Let's see.
According to the map, we need to keep heading west.
How much further do we have to go?
Uh.
Easy, buddy.
It's only been half an hour.
This seems a little excessive.
But just think.
All this money can get you a
lot of weed.
Oh my gosh.
A whole lot of weed.
Who needs the weed?
Okay, so you guys are just being silly now.
The map says we need to go this way.
So let's go that way.
Coming?
I'm going back.
I'll see you guys back at the house.
Bye, boss.
This is beautiful.
You're beautiful.
Why don't we take a moment and
look at the map.
Okay.
Hey there, Willow.
I'm not going back anymore.
And I told you I'd respect that
and leave you alone.
But I couldn't help it.
I was walking through the woods today
and I found this
this pinecone.
And it brought me right back to that wonderful night
we spent together under the stars.
Me, you, and the pinecone.
I miss you, my little wispy willow.
Ready?
Lead the way.
Fifteen men of them good and true
Yo-ho-ho
and a bottle of rum
Each of the men
step with a pew
Yo-ho-ho
and a bottle of rum
That's awesome.
The costume, the
the vibe.
It's a very Treasure Island
and I dig it.
Where's my manners?
Come on.
Ah!
Are you one of Preston's actor friends?
Did he bring you to this island
to freak us out and make this all
realistic and shit like?
It's not working.
Don't tell him that.
Do you...
Do you go to college for that shit?
Do you like go, I'm gonna be an actor and go to college
or...
Does that be dumb?
I saw you last night.
You were with that goth
chick, right?
You were with the goth chick.
Is she your girlfriend?
I swear to God, I did not
touch her.
I didn't touch her. I looked a couple times.
I looked a couple times. I mean, I...
You gotta look sometimes.
You know what I'm saying?
All I care for
is my gold.
The game? Like...
I dropped out
of the game.
Let's just go back.
Like...
I'm a little too high for this method
acting bullshit. I mean...
Drop the act. I mean, you just go back to the
house and I gotta be a...
...
woods where shadows play lies a fork to guide your way beneath the oak with leaves of green
lies a clue that must be seen take three paces turn around face the sunset hear the sound
hear the wind blow through the trees to lead you where the treasure flees listen to nature's subtle
call to find the richest one at all okay um three paces sunset oak leaves that way it's that way
angela it's definitely that way come on hey you good not even close how long have you been seeing
him again what i went through your phone and saw the text how could you violate my privacy
no acknowledgement and straight to gaslighting
where are you going where i should have gone months ago
i'm out
judging sun's out where a woman had been yo ho ho and a bottle of rum was she a wench or a shuddering
maid brave the knife and took the blade by god she had enough for a clucky jade yo ho ho and a bottle
who poking in to love her
ethan help let the girl go
not another step or she goes overboard what do you want you want what is rightfully mine you have it
what are you talking about you have one as well give it to me this stupid thing
you'll let her go if I give it to you I am NOT here to parlay okay okay please
just don't hurt her no he just terrified me it's happening oh no I can't let this
go this don't do it lad this one is not worth your blood
you could have left
something to think
don't hurt him I'll do anything you want just don't hurt him
anything you say yes willow no just just run away do you love him truly not
looking good
I ask again, do you truly love him?
Yes, yes.
Hurry, Willa.
I'm so sorry.
Me too.
Willa.
Would you die for him?
I ask again, would you die for him?
Sorry, lad.
Some wenches aren't worth it.
Willa!
Let this be a lesson I don't need you to trust, boy.
Oh, Harlan!
Oh!
Oh, shiver me timbers!
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, man.
Damn, Grover.
You've been giving me the best rides of my life.
You know, whenever you're ready, we should probably go again.
Again?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll give you the best two minutes of your life.
What if next time we shoot for, like, four minutes?
Four minutes?
I mean, yeah.
Four minutes, girl.
Just give me, like, five.
Ten.
Thirty.
An hour.
Give me an hour.
And then when I come back, I'll give you that four minutes.
Maybe if you do that thing with your leg in the end.
No, then that'll be about two and a half.
But don't do the thing with the leg.
I'll be back.
You stay right there looking sexy.
Just like that.
Mwah.
Beautiful.
I've got to be right back.
Oh, boy.
How much farther do you think we have to go?
Well, one way to find out.
Should we have left some breadcrumbs or something?
Where did we get the bread from?
That makes some sense, Angela.
Good point.
Hey! Help! Over here!
What the?
Oh, no, no, it's part of the game, so I'm going to have to free her.
No, this is definitely not a part of the game.
Can you please get me out of here?
Uh...
Ruby?
These...
These are real.
I think she's really trapped in here.
How did this happen?
Long story.
Well, springy might take a long time, so...
Night.
It involves an ancient curse.
A resurrected pirate seeking revenge.
Basically, the story I told you before is true.
Cross is here.
Okay, that was kind of a short story.
But, um, Angela, any thoughts?
Because she's talking crazy for sure.
Um...
Don't worry.
This should do the trick.
This is going to work.
We'll get you out of here.
We'll get you some medical attention, okay?
Thank you both.
But I do not need medical help.
Everything I told you is true.
And not a dead man's chest.
Who's singing?
It's too late!
Hide!
Hide, you.
...
Now where did my witchy little rat run off to?
You'll find us.
I have to give myself up.
Fuck.
It's insane. There's three of us and one of him. We could just take him out and escape.
What part of ghost pirate do you not understand?
If I go out there, you too can escape. He'll kill you. I can handle myself.
I think I can get him to spare me. He might need me for something.
I'll distract him.
There you are, bitch. Scurry off to hide like the rat you are.
Oh, no, no, no. I was just playing a game. And you won.
Another game?
Can you still appreciate dark beauty?
I've got to get the fuck out of here.
Now I smell the remnants of my gold. They were here. Where did they go?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Do you know what the term cleave them to the brisket means?
You slice somebody.
From the shoulder to...
To the belly.
Their insides fall at their feet.
You force them to watch as they slowly and painfully die.
I know where they're going.
Leave the way.
All right, come on. Let's keep going.
So that wasn't real back there, right?
Honestly, Angel, I'm not 100% sure myself. So whatever's going on is insane.
What if there are...
There's a couple and they're just into some freaky deaky stuff.
Angel, I wish that's what it was, but this is beyond my understanding.
So we need to get back to the house. We need to figure out what's going on.
Okay, come on.
Whoo.
Come on.
God damn it. These things are so stupid. I told you they get caught on everything.
I'll help you, Ruby.
Give me a second. No, Angel, I can do it myself because you're just going to end up...
Yeah.
There you go.
Yeah, okay. Guess I'm done with these then. Thank you so much, Angela.
Thank you for your help.
This rock... Yeah.
You know what? This is...
I'm really sorry about you...
It's fine. I don't even like them anyway.
Get them off.
Do you need help?
No, Angel, no more help. Thank you.
Okay.
Ugh.
Have a mess.
No!
Okay.
The sun's starting to set.
It should be back by now.
Well.
Time to prepare the festivities.
Yeah.
Get in.
Wait, wait, wait...
Tell me you heard that.
No, they can't have reached us already!
Okay.
Ah... Let's hide.
Slowly, slowly.
Ethan!
What happened to you?
Is it a snake?
You won't believe me.
Oh, I'm sure we will.
It was attacked by some zombie pirate-looking guy.
No, no, no.
We were too.
That's what happened to us.
It is impossible, but
I don't know, it seems like
the story is true and Captain Roger Cross
is back or something.
Where's Willow?
Is she okay?
Tried to save her.
Brett's gone, too.
I don't think any of us are safe.
Austin?
No, I didn't see him.
But he would have never left Brett.
He's gone, too.
Okay, it's okay, buddy.
We just barely
escaped ourselves.
We need to get back
to the house. We'll be okay at the house.
Can you move? Can you walk?
Maybe, maybe, with help.
Okay, come on.
You're in my light, baby.
Preston, seriously.
Preston?
Preston!
Hey!
Ethan!
Hey, Ethan!
What the hell is going on?
The ghost pirate guy is back.
He got Ethan. He attacked us.
He has your Godmaid and
Britt and Austin and Willow.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Britt, Willow, Austin...
They're dead.
Hey, don't even play like this.
I'm not!
What are you talking about?
I just told you, we have to leave.
How do we get off this island?
Okay, all right, listen, Preston, I know.
I need you to focus right now, okay?
And figure out how we're going to get off the island.
The ferry, but it doesn't come till tomorrow morning.
Can we call that?
No, there's no service here.
Well, that's just ridiculous.
We're on an island backed up by nothing but generators, okay?
Do you see any telephone poles or lines anywhere?
What can we leave?
There's a satellite phone by the docks.
Okay, awesome.
You, me, we're going to the satellite phone.
You stay here with Ethan.
Got it.
Okay, lead the way.
Harley!
You let her go!
Another step in my direction, and alas, we'll get a new smile ear to ear.
Please help me!
Hold on, babe.
Let me take a wild guess.
You want money, right?
Just my gold.
Return it, and this nightmare ends.
What are you talking about?
I think he means these.
Take them and let her go.
No, no.
We're still alive, are we?
We end this our way.
Ah!
Inside the house.
I can't protect you, I can't hear the noise.
Ah!
Ethan!
The actual fuck is going on right now.
Harley.
What are you doing?
Ah!
Don't follow me!
Rest in peace.
What are you looking for?
What are you...
Oh, my God.
If you want to survive, I suggest you move.
Preston, move.
Let her work.
Move!
What is that?
We need a barrier.
This is common rocks, so it won't last long, but it'll buy us some time.
This will be the last time you interfere with me, witch.
It won't last long.
Even now, the blood moon rises, and this curse will be at its fullest, and I will enter.
Believe me when I say, no quarter will be given.
Hmm.
I meant to say, you know my trajectory.
tar点
ы
Can somebody please tell me
why creepy old pirate dude back there is killing all my friends.
If you don't mind, perhaps I should appreciate it.
It started 300 years ago.
It...
It has to be a program.
This is a story
Veiled by the shadows of time
A story of love, treachery, and of a curse
That has haunted my bloodline for generations
Long ago, on this very island
My ancestor stood
Her heart entwined with that of Captain Rotary Cross
But their love was eclipsed
By betrayal and greed
Deep in the archives of my family home
I uncovered a map, a cryptic guide
That led directly to the very gold the cross could never find
And as I delved further into the folklore
The story came to life
In my pursuit, I exhausted all the resources
Until I met Preston
Whose wealth became available
The tool necessary for the expedition
To find the stolen gold
Now make no mistake
This gold is more than mere metal
It is the tool necessary
To break the curse
And end the torment of my family
To bring cross to corporeal form
A dark ritual was necessary
A sacrifice
The blood of a fish
A fisherman mingled with the gold
An unholy offering
To summon cross from the abyss
And now he exists in a form
That can reunite with his stolen gold
And once he has retrieved all the gold
He will return to human form
At which point I can fulfill my destiny
To end the curse
To end him
And the curse that is haunted by bloodline
Our fates are intertwined
Only together can we face the looming darkness
So brace yourselves
For the blood moon approaches
Yes?
So, let me get this straight
Cause my comprehension skills
Really ain't all that good
So, from your story
You tricked me
Murdered some dude
Which brought back
This demon pirate
Who killed most of my friends
Who'll probably kill all of us here tonight
All because you wanted to break some
Generational curse
I mean, yes
But, like I said
Our destinies are intertwined
My fate is to break the curse
And blood had to be spilled
For the greater good
Yeah...
Nah, bitch
That ain't it
You gotta go
Come on
No, what are you doing?
What?
You know you need me
Not that much
No
No, no
No, no, no
Let me in
I'm your only chance to survive
No fucking way
I like the rest of our friends too
Yeah, I can still help you
Listen, your goals
All of your goals
It's right inside
You can get this
And then
You get your revenge on them
The only one I want revenge on is you
No, please
No
Let the water cleanse you
No, please
I can't
Fine
No, let me in
Yes, you love me
Never
Say no
No, please
Please
I'm young
Let me in
What do you mean?
I'm the reason
I don't understand
Or even know
What you've done
No
Bye
Peace
They're all mine
well that just happened yeah should you have done that hey right or wrong she was responsible for
all of us so what's the plan then i know what i'm gonna do i'm gonna take this bottle of wine
i'm gonna go and draw myself a bath i'm gonna get in that bath to wash away this awful day
off of me and then whatever this is maybe we'll be over once i'm done
but i don't think that i don't care i am done
bye
well i have an idea
we have to end cross and get off of this damn island from what soraya said once he gets his
gold he's more or less human and killable so we give him his gold and when he's whole we end him
before he can end us
there's three of us and one of him so the math's on our side
okay let's kill us a 300 year old pirate
okay yeah sure no problem it's good yeah that felt good we're fucked yeah
definitely yes this sucks
it's time
okay so we count to three open the door
and give him hell yeah that's the plan
oh it's just too late to back out because that bath with harley sucks
very good
okay guys come on we got this it's for ethan and willow and brit and austin
what about kip
i don't know about him but i'm pretty sure one way or another he's gone too
guys i'm really hoping that's because i forgot to pay the electric bill
looks like he decided to come to us
guys the barrier's dead
he's going to help us
why are you doing this
is fine
what's the paper
um
this whole thing
what is it
come to work
what are you updated about
it's no corner
keep it
oh my god
c'mon
this is such a
uh
fuck
goddammit come on
oh
no uh
come on we need to work as a team
Honestly, it's not working, Ruby.
Well, what are we supposed to do?
No, you can get the hell out of here.
What the fuck are you going to do?
Hey, hey, I got it.
I fucking hope so.
All right.
It's just me and you.
Mono e mono, you crusty piece of shit.
You flipped the wrong flapjack, buddy.
What?
No honor?
You have no right to die with us, boy.
All right, it's now or never.
Just follow my lead.
You have the coins?
Ruby, before we do this,
there's something I need to tell you.
Angela, whatever it is, it can wait, okay?
We need to do this.
You want these?
You want to parlay?
No.
I know you won't give quarter.
I just want a fair fight.
After centuries, the curse is broken and I live again.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha!
No!
Play you too, Takengan.
What's your name, lass?
You must know, it's Ruby.
Oh, is that funny to you?
No treasure is complete without a Ruby.
Help!
No!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Please!
Oh, no, no, no!
Angelo, no, no, no!
Oh, God, why did you do that?
Why?
Please!
Okay, alright.
Yeah, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
Okay.
I just want to tell you how I feel about you.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, Angelo.
No, Angelo, I always knew, I always knew, you dummy.
Like a ship lost at sea, love is destined to sink to the depths, forsaken and forgotten.
This ends now.
Yeah!
Oh!
Hey!
Let's get out of here!
Ugh!
Hey!
Ugh, argh, argh!
Fine!
Ugh!
Take this!
Ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh!
Meh!
Eh, ugh!
I'm sorry that you never had true love, but none of that had anything to do with any of us!
The only thing I love is gold. And lead.
El Davy Jones, we said what's up?
You savvy?
Preston! Oh, God. Oh, you're okay.
Okay. Okay. You're okay? Oh, God. Okay, enough? Okay, okay.
Angelo's?
Yeah, yeah. I'm so glad he finally told you.
He's the worst timing.
The fucking worst.
Let's go get a pizza or something.
The satellite phone worked eventually.
So, hope's on the way.
Man, I hate this fucking place.
Island paradises suck ass.
Yep.
That was exactly what I needed.
What did I miss, though? Story time? Tell me everything?
Hey, did I tell you how much I fucking love this girl?
Oh, my God. Are you shot?
That's just a flesh wound.
Come here, girl.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You know, I do still want a destination wedding, though.
Let's not do a pirate's beach.
Maybe do something landlocked at this time.
Hey, Ruby, what do you say? You want to be my best man, woman, person?
I just need somebody to keep this chicken check.
You know what I'm saying?
I don't know, Preston.
I think I might be done with your vacations for a while.
Oh, okay. Fair enough.
I'm gonna wipe out.
I'm yours.
The blood red,
blood red beach.
The
blood red,
blood red beach.
Beneath the line
of the blood red moon
A interpretation of a swang
Lay in a gale howling tune
Walked something
not dead or alive
He haunts this place
His pain still survives
A curse of the hag
The love of a witch
His heart of blaze
He torments that bitch
Greed and hate
Sully the sad
He's this morning
The magic of the hagg
He's gonna go back to the blackbeard
Blood, bloodbath
Bloodbath
Son of a bitch
Damn
I think you know a guy
Shares some weeds
Shares some stories
He haunts my ass out
Motherfucker
Greed and hate
Sully the sad
He's this morning
The magic of the hagg
He's gonna go back to the blackbeard
Blood, bloodbath
Bloodbath
Thank you.